Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum C
Yale University Divinity School Library
United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum C
1895-1994
RG 11C
Yale University Divinity School Library
38
(38 boxes)
This record group represents a continuation of the official archives of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, supplementing and overlapping the papers in record groups 11, 11A, and 11B. It provides extensive information about the institutions and projects to which the United Board lent its support. The United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia supports educational work in China, Hong Kong, India, Indonesia, Japan, Korea, Pakistan, The Philippines, Republic of China (Taiwan).
United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Deposited by the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
Biographical / Historical
Detailed information about the work of the United Board for Christian Higher Education during the period represented by these archives is contained in Paul Lauby's book Sailing on Winds of Change: Two Decades in the Life of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1969-1990.
Scope and Contents
I. Committee Records
II. History and Program Documentation
III. Consolidated General File
IV. China Files
The records date primarily from 1979 to 1990. Very little processing of the records has been done; the folders have been ordered and described as received. Record Group No. 11C covers the period of time when the UBCHEA was beginning to reinstitute programs in the People's Republic of China. Most of these China program files are in Series IV, but Series I, II, and III also contain some China-related material. Files related to institutions and programs in other Asian countries are primarily included in Series III, the Consolidated General File.
Arrangement
I. Committee Records
II. History and Program Documentation
III. Consolidated General File
IV. China Files
Religious education -- Asia; Universities and colleges -- Asia; Educators; United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
- Committee Records, Series I
  - Board of Trustees
    - Semi-annual meetings, 1988 May, 1987 Nov (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Semi-annual meetings, 1987 May, 1986 Nov (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Semi-annual meetings, 1986 May, 1985 Nov (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Semi-annual meetings, 1985 May, 1984 Nov (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Semi-annual meetings, 1984 May, 1983 Nov (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Semi-annual meetings, 1983 May, 1982 Nov (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Semi-annual meetings, 1982 May, 1981 Nov (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Semi-annual meetings, 1981 May, 1980 Nov (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Semi-annual meetings, 1980 May, 1979 Nov (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Personnel Resources Committee (see also Asia-North American Faculty Exchange Program)
    - Records, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Personnel Subcommittee: China Program
    - Records, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Records, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Records, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Records, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Development Committee
    - Records, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Records, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Records, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Records, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Executive Committee
    - Records, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Records, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Records, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Records, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Records, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Finance Administration Committee
    - Records, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Records, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Records, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Records, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Records, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Investment and Banking Committee
    - Records, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Records, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Records, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Records, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Records, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Records, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Nominations Committee
    - Records, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Records, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Records, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Records, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Social Responsibility for Investment Committee
    - Records, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Records, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Investments Social Policy Statement (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - University Programs Committee
    - Records, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Records, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Records, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Records, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Other committees and groups
    - Lists of Trustees, Counselors, Committee members, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Trustee/Counselor Development Goals, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Evaluation Committee (Board of Trustees), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Task Force on Staffing and Organization, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Church Trustees Consultation (Mission Denominations), 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Counselors of United Board, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Counselors of United Board - dinner meeting, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Audit Subcommittees, 1983-1987 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - United Board Trustees: Five Year Support Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- History and Program Documentation, Series II
  - General
    - Reports of UBCHEA President to Board of Trustees, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - "Directions for the '90's" - draft, planning document, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Singapore Consultation - Planning for the '90's, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - "Case Statement for UBCHEA", 1981 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - "Directions for the '80's" - planning document; revised planning document; report of the Review and Rethinking Committee, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Symposium; "Light in the East" art exhibit; "United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia 50 Years" (booklet), 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Speeches: "Our Future in Asia" by Nathan M. Pusey; "Fiify Years United" by Andrew Roy, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - China Program (see also Series IV)
    - China Program background and development, incl. "Minute between the UBCHEA and the Chinese Society for Education" (1980), 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - China Program documentation, 1983-1992 (Box 3, Folder 59-60)
    - Dr. C. T. Hu, Director of China Program; papers, reports, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 61-62)
    - Re. 60th anniversary of University of Nanking, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Exchange and Library Programs
    - Asia-North America Educational Exchange Program: Report on Consultation; announcements of program, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Asia-North America Faculty Exchange Program/ Asia-North America Visiting Professors Program; applications, 1987-1991 (Box 3, Folder 65-68)
    - Asia-North America Faculty Exchange Program/ Asia-North America Visiting Professors Program; corres., announcements, 1987-1991 (Box 3, Folder 69-70)
    - Council of International Educational Exchange, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Faculty Development (US) - New Visiting Scholars Program, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 72-73)
    - Amity Foundation program for sending teachers of English to China, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - NCCCUSA program for sending teachers of English to China; Franklin Woo, Judy Manton (consultant), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Amity Foundation/ NCCCUSA program for sending teachers of English to China, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Visiting Scholars - insurance, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Library development Program, 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Other programs, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Project evaluations (2 loose leaf notebooks), 1980-1981 (Box 4)
  - Conferences, events
    - Singapore Consultation - Planning for the '90's, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Asian Christian University Professors' Fellowship, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Conference of Asian Religion and the Arts (CARA), Bali, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Conference of Asian Religion and the Arts (CARA), Manila, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Religion and Art committee meeting, Hong Kong, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Asian Interfaith Conference on Religion and the Arts, Chiang Mai, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - "Breaking Barriers: Religions and their Arts in Asia; A Colleciton of Essays" from Chiang Mai meeting on Religions and the Arts, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - "Mission of the Asian Christian College Today" - Asian Small College Workshop, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Asian Conference on Science, Faith, and Justice, Manila, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Asian Conference: "The Future: Science, Faith, and Justice in Asia", Chiang Mai, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Women's Concerns Conference, Chiang Mai, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Women's Concerns Conference, Satya Wacana Univ., Indonesia, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Consultation on Women's Concerns, Hong Kong, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Consultation on Christian Concerns in Higher Education, Chiang Mai, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Women's Studies Seminar, Chiang Mai, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Consultation on Women's Studies, Lady Doak College, Madurai, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Asian Women's Career Planning Consultation, Singapore, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 96-97)
    - Asian Women's Career Conference, Manila, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 98-101)
    - Asian Traditional Music Workshop, Bali, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Folk Religions Conference (proposed), 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Association of Christian Colleges of Medicine in Asia (ACCMA), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Conference of Christian Medical Colleges of Asia, Vellore, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 105-106)
    - China Archival meeting (Arthur Waldron proposal), 1986 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Conference on Christianity in China, Stony Point (John K. Fairbank et al), 1983 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Sino-American Educational and Cultural Exchange: Comparative Experience, Conference at East-West Center, Honolulu, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Asian Trustees/ Principals' Consultation, Bangalore, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Asian Trustees Consultation, Hong Kong, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - First International Conference on Literature and Religion (2 oversize volumes of material), 1986 (Box 7)
- Consolidated General File, Series III
  - A - General
    - A, 1980-1985 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Abercrombie, Clarence L., 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - ACCMA ( Association of Christian Colleges of Medicine in Asia), 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - ACUCA (Association of Christian Universities and Colleges in Asia) - printed material, 1986-1991 (Box 39, Folder 1374)
    - ACUCA - proposals, grants, reports, 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 115-116)
    - American Bureau for Medical Advancement in China, 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - American Committees for Human Rights, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Anderson, Delbert E. (UB Trustee), 1980-1985 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Anderson, Edward F., 1980-1988 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Anderson, Gerald H., 1980-1985 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - APECA (Assoc. of Psychological and Educational Counselors of Asia), 1980-1985 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Applicants for UB positions, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Armstrong, Mrs. H. Parr, 1972-1987 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Asia-North America Educational Exchange Committee, 1976-1985 (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Asia Society, The, 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - Asian A-Z (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Asian Education Digest (UBCHEA publication), 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Asian Institute of Technology, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - Asian Women's Institute: Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Asian Women's Institute: Proposals, grants, 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Asian Women's Institute: Publications and printed matter (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - Association of Korean Christian Scholars in North America, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - ATSSEA (Assoc. of Theological Schools in Southeast Asia), 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Atwater, Mrs. R. B. (Betty), 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Ayars, Ms. Christine M. (estate of), 1980 (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - AZFAR Foundation, The Jawaid Book Publication PRogram in URdu, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 137)
  - B - General
    - Baber, Mrs. Ray E. (Elizabeth), 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 138)
    - Baker, Rev. Gilbert, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 138)
    - Baldi, Carol H., 1977-1987 (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - Bankers Life (UB pension plan), 1971-1986 (Box 9, Folder 140)
    - Barker, Mrs. Lee V. (Marjorie R.), 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 141)
    - Bartholomew, Alfred C., 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 142)
    - Batoon, Reuben R., 1982-1988 (Box 9, Folder 143)
    - Beaver, Raymond W., 1983 (Box 9, Folder 144)
    - Beck, Dr. and Mrs. Harrell F., 1983-1988 (Box 9, Folder 145)
    - Becker, Dr. and Mrs. Stewart, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 146)
    - Belton, Donald, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 147)
    - Bennett A-Z (Box 9, Folder 148)
    - Bernardez family, 1982-1988 (Box 9, Folder 149)
    - Beshar, Robert P., 1980-1988 (Box 9, Folder 150)
    - Best, Ernest E., 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 151)
    - Bhandhachat, Prasert, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 152)
    - Biggs, John (John Biggs Consort, performing artists), 1978-1984 (Box 9, Folder 153)
    - Bingham, Dr. and Mrs. Woodbridge (Ursula), 1980-1987 (Box 9, Folder 154)
    - Blatchford, Charles H., 1976-1981 (Box 9, Folder 155)
    - Blue Cross/ Blue Shield - UB staff medical coverage, 1972-1987 (Box 9, Folder 156)
    - Br (Box 9, Folder 157)
    - Brentlinger, James L., 1980-1985 (Box 9, Folder 158)
    - Bresnan, James L., 1980-1985 (Box 9, Folder 159)
    - Bridenbaugh, Jennie B. (estate of), 1981 (Box 9, Folder 160)
    - Brown, Alex Sons (broker), 1980-1986 (Box 9, Folder 161)
    - Brown, Mrs. Vansant Jenkins (estate of), 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 162)
    - Bruggers, Glenn, 1980-1987 (Box 9, Folder 163)
    - Bu (Box 9, Folder 164)
    - Burnham, Frederic, 1980-1988 (Box 9, Folder 165)
  - C - General
    - C (Box 9, Folder 166)
    - Campbell, Donald A. Co. (fundraising firm), 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 167)
    - Carder, Cecil B., 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 168)
    - Carey, E. Frank, 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 169)
    - Carlander, Dr. and Mrs. Kenneth D., 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 170)
    - Carle, Robert (Church Divinity School of the Pacific), 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 171)
    - Carleton College, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 172)
    - Catalano, Raymond A., 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 173)
    - Catholic Forum on China, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 174)
    - Ceniza, Dr. and Mrs. Claro (Riorita), 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 175)
    - Central A-Z (Box 9, Folder 176)
    - Central Christian Church (Clearwater, FL), 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 177)
    - Centre for Society and Religion, Sri Lanka, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 178)
    - Cha (Box 9, Folder 179)
    - Chandekar, Ramesh, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 180)
    - Chang, Dr. and Mrs. C. H. Joseph, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 181)
    - Che (Box 9, Folder 182)
    - Chen, William K. W., 1984 (Box 9, Folder 183)
    - Chi (Box 9, Folder 184)
    - Chiang Mai Mission Board, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 185)
    - China Medical Board of New York, 1980-1987 (Box 9, Folder 186)
    - Cho (Box 9, Folder 187)
    - Christian A-Z (Box 9, Folder 188)
    - Christian Conference of Asia, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 189)
    - Chu, Samuel, 1980-1985 (Box 9, Folder 190)
    - Church Women United, 1980-1985 (Box 9, Folder 191)
    - Cl - Co (Box 9, Folder 192)
    - Claremont Colleges, 1980-1983 (Box 10, Folder 193)
    - Claremont United Church of Christ, 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 194)
    - Clark, Charles H., 1981-1984 (Box 10, Folder 195)
    - Clark, Eugene, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 196)
    - Clymer, Kenton J., 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 197)
    - Coles, J. Ackerman (estate of), 1980-1987 (Box 10, Folder 198)
    - Colonial Consulting Corp., 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 199)
    - Commission of Women and Work, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 200)
    - Committee on International Relations Studies, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 201)
    - Cooley, Frank, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 202)
    - Corbett, Elizabeth, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 203)
    - Corporate contributions A-Z, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 204)
    - Council A-Z (Box 10, Folder 205)
    - Council for International Exchange of Scholars, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 206)
    - Cr (Box 10, Folder 207)
    - Crawford, Robert H., 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 208)
    - Cross, Mrs. Rowland M. (Rebecca), 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 209)
  - D - Denominations
    - American Baptist Churches USA, 1980-1986 (Box 10, Folder 210-213)
    - American Baptist Churches USA - Am. Baptist Foreign Mission Society, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 214)
    - Christian Church (Disciples of Christ), 1980-1986 (Box 10, Folder 215-218)
    - Episcopal Church, 1980-1987 (Box 10, Folder 219-222)
    - Lutheran Church in America, 1980-1987 (Box 10, Folder 223-226)
    - American Lutheran Church, 1981-1987 (Box 10, Folder 227-228)
    - Presbyterian Church in Canada, 1980-1986 (Box 10, Folder 229-231)
    - Presbyterian Church in the USA, General Assembly Mission Board, Atlanta, 1980-1986 (Box 10, Folder 232-236)
    - United Presbyterian Church USA, Program Agency, NYC, 1980-1988 (Box 10, Folder 237-244)
    - Reformed Church in America, 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 245-247)
    - United Church of Canada, 1980-1987 (Box 10, Folder 248-253)
    - United Church of Christ, Board of Homeland Ministries, 1980-1986 (Box 11, Folder 254)
    - United Church of Christ, Board for World Ministries, 1980-1987 (Box 11, Folder 255-260)
    - United Methodist Church, 1981-1987 (Box 11, Folder 261-269)
  - D - General
    - D (Box 11, Folder 270-271)
    - Dando, William A. (Univ. of North Dakota), 1980-1988 (Box 11, Folder 272)
    - Davis, Russell C. Jr., 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 273)
    - De (Box 11, Folder 274)
    - Decker, John W., 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 275)
    - Denny, Dr. and Mrs. Wayne B., 1980-1987 (Box 11, Folder 276)
    - Dickinson, Dr. and Mrs. Raymond L., 1980-1987 (Box 11, Folder 277-278)
    - Diener, Paul W., 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 279)
    - Dunn, Eleanor, 1980-1987 (Box 11, Folder 280)
  - E - General
    - E (Box 11, Folder 281)
    - East Bay Committee for UBCHEA, 1980-1986 (Box 11, Folder 282-283)
    - East-West Center, 1980-1986 (Box 11, Folder 284)
    - Ecumenical Development Co-operative society (EDCS), 1980-1986 (Box 11, Folder 285-287)
    - Ellinwood, DeWitt C., 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 288)
    - Erwin, Mr. and Mrs. Holmes T., 1980-1987 (Box 11, Folder 289)
    - Esterline, Mr. and Mrs. John, 1982-1987 (Box 11, Folder 290)
    - Everett, William Johnson (Candler School of Theology), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 291)
  - F - General
    - F (Box 11, Folder 292)
    - Fairbank, John K. (Harvard), 1980-1984 (Box 12, Folder 293)
    - Fiftieth anniversary files - general, worship service, lecture tour (Box 12, Folder 294-297)
    - Fiala, Dr. and Mrs. Robert, 1980-1986 (Box 12, Folder 298)
    - First Presbyterian Church, Charlotte, NC, 1981-1984 (Box 12, Folder 299)
    - Fisher, Alzo John - Memorial Endowment Fund, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 300)
    - Flaherty, Donald W., 1980-1983 (Box 12, Folder 301)
    - Flores, Pedro V. (International Development Research Center), 1980-1989 (Box 12, Folder 302)
    - Frei, Rev. and Mrs. Ernest J. (Winifred), 1980-1984 (Box 12, Folder 303)
    - Fulton, Robert Brank, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 304)
    - Furuya, Keiichi, 1980-1985 (Box 12, Folder 305-306)
  - F - Foundations and trusts
    - General, 1980-1986 (Box 12, Folder 307-309)
    - A (Box 12, Folder 310)
    - Asia Foundation, 1980-1985 (Box 12, Folder 311)
    - Kresge Foundation, 1980-1987 (Box 12, Folder 312)
    - Luce Foundation, Henry, 1980-1986 (Box 12, Folder 313-314)
    - McBrier Trust, Edwin M., 1980-1985 (Box 12, Folder 315)
    - McGraw-Hill Foundation, 1980-1984 (Box 12, Folder 316)
    - Macy Foundation, Josiah, Jr., 1980-1983 (Box 12, Folder 317)
    - Meek Foundation (Mr. and Mrs. Samuel W. Meek), 1980-1983 (Box 12, Folder 318)
    - Merrill Trust, Charles E., 1980-1983 (Box 12, Folder 319)
    - Shu Foundation (Dr. F. M. S. Shu), 1980-1987 (Box 12, Folder 320)
    - West Foundation (Mrs. Harold B. West), 1980-1984 (Box 12, Folder 321)
    - Wood Foundation (Mary Elizabeth Wood), 1980-1986 (Box 12, Folder 322)
  - G - General
    - Gambrell, Mrs. Charles G., 1980-1984 (Box 12, Folder 323)
    - Ganfield, Mr. and Mrs. A. Boardman, 1980-1988 (Box 12, Folder 324)
    - George, Mary Belle, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 325)
    - Global Education Associates, 1980-1986 (Box 12, Folder 326)
    - Goetcheus, Vernon M., 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 327)
    - Goldome (New York Bank for Savings), 1980-1985 (Box 12, Folder 328)
    - Granner, Justine E., 1980-1985 (Box 13, Folder 329)
    - Graves, Mr. and Mrs. Alfred J., 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 330)
    - Gray, Dorothy Landis, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 331)
    - Gregory, Dr. and Mrs. Paul R., 1980-1988 (Box 13, Folder 332)
    - Grether, Dr. and Mrs. Herbert, 1980-1984 (Box 13, Folder 333)
  - H - General
    - Ha - Hi (Box 13, Folder 334)
    - Hammond, Dr. and Mrs. Ray K., 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 335)
    - Hartford Committee, 1964-1981 (Box 13, Folder 336)
    - Harvard University A-Z (Box 13, Folder 337)
    - Harvard University: Chai K. Imm (Center for International Affairs), 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 338)
    - Harvard-Yenching Institute - proposals, grants, corres., 1980-1986 (Box 13, Folder 339-345)
    - Harvard-Yenching Institute - board meetings, minutes, financial statements, 1980-1989 (Box 13, Folder 346-353)
    - Hass, Dr. and Mrs. Warren J., 1980-1985 (Box 13, Folder 354)
    - Hawaii Loa College, 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 355)
    - Heimburger, Richard A., 1980-1985 (Box 13, Folder 356)
    - Helsabeck, Dr. and Mrs. Robert E. (Mary V.), 1982-1986 (Box 13, Folder 357)
    - Herolz, Geneva Bane (estate of), 1981 (Box 13, Folder 358)
    - Hess, Edwin A., 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 359)
    - Hilscher, Harris G., 1980 (Box 13, Folder 360)
    - Hinkley, Lelia M., 1980-1987 (Box 13, Folder 361)
    - Ho - Hs (Box 13, Folder 362)
    - Hogue, Harland E., 1980 (Box 13, Folder 363)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace (archives), 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 364)
    - How, Bang How Memorial Scholarship (Mrs. Julie How Hwa), 1980 (Box 13, Folder 365)
    - Howell, Almonte C., 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 366)
    - Howson, Mrs. Herbert A. (Gertrude F.), 1980-1985 (Box 13, Folder 367)
    - Hsieh, Chiao-min (James), 1985-1987 (Box 13, Folder 368)
    - Hsung, Ray-may (Tunghai University), 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 369)
    - Hu, Mr. and Mrs. David Yu (Box 13, Folder 370)
    - Huang, Raymond (retired president of Lingnan College), 1980-1988 (Box 13, Folder 371)
    - Hutchison, Dr. and Mrs. Bruce, 1980-1985 (Box 13, Folder 372)
  - H - Hong Kong
    - Chung Chi College
      - General correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 14, Folder 373)
      - Finance and disbursements, 1980-1985 (Box 14, Folder 374)
      - Library (Mrs. Sylvia Shen), 1980-1984 (Box 14, Folder 375)
      - Printed material, 1980-1986 (Box 14, Folder 376)
      - Shen, Philip, 1980-1986 (Box 14, Folder 377)
      - Fu, Philip, 1980-1988 (Box 14, Folder 378-379)
      - Proposals, grants, reports, 1980-1986 (Box 14, Folder 380-381)
      - Tam, S. W., 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 382)
      - Project evaluations, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 383)
      - Scholarship reports, 1980-1988 (Box 14, Folder 384)
    - Hong Kong Baptist College
      - General correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 14, Folder 385)